(忆往昔)
辛格先生
Mr. Singer.
你的时辰到了
Your time's up.
鲍比  鲍比
Bobby! Bobby!
小混球
Idjits.
鲍比
Bobby? Hey!
你真想困在这儿
You really want to get stuck...
变成鬼魂吗
turn into some ghost?
我知道我在做什么  鲁弗斯
I know what I'm doing, Rufus.
你在想你能帮助那俩小子
You're thinking you can help those boys.
但是你遇见几个头脑正常的鬼魂
But how many sprits you meet in their right mind?
你怎么打算  是走是留
What's it gonna be -- stay or go?
我担心鲍比也许一直跟着你们
I'm concerned that Bobby might be haunting you.
我已试过和鲍比联系
I've already tried contacting Bobby.
不叫上我
Without me?
如果他在的话  我就会告诉你了
If he was there, I'd have told you.
我们把他火葬了  迪恩
We burned him, Dean.
那把剑从屋子另一边飞到我手里
The blade was across the room, and then it was in my hand.
然后我的酒自己没了
My beer drank itself.
还有  那页书奇迹般的出现在床上
That page magically appeared on the bed.
鲍比的书自己掉了下来
Bobby's book fell down,
找到小卡那人的号码自动掉了出来
and out popped the number of the guy who found cass.
那不是鲍比
It's not Bobby!
有可能啊
It could be.
-不  不可能  -为什么
- No, it couldn't be! - Why not?
因为那是我们一厢情愿
Because we want it to be.
即使普通人  也能到处看到死去的人
Regular people -- they see ones they lost everywhere, too.
没错  那叫鬼
Yeah, freakin' ghosts.
或者只是因为他们太想念那些人了
Or they just miss them a lot.
如果那是鲍比  他会让我们知道的
If it was Bobby, he would let us know.
该死
Balls!
(如今)
好了  开吃吧
All right, here we go.
你知道吗
You know...
就算整个世界天翻地覆了
even though the world is going to crap,
有样东西总是靠得住
there's one thing that I can always count on --
这玩意儿的口味始终如一
these things tasting the same
我们伟大的祖国每家小店都一个样
in every drive-through in every state in our great nation.
安妮
Annie.
迪恩
Hey, Dean.
真是意外  你最近怎样
A nice surprise. How you been?
我还活着  所以算是不错吧
Oh, I'm still kicking. So, good, I guess.
我听说了鲍比的事
Heard about Bobby.
节哀
I'm sorry.
是啊  你也是
Yeah. Us too.
怎么了
What's up?
我这儿还有他一些旧书
Well, I got some of his old books.
你想要吗
I thought maybe you'd want them.
好啊  你在哪
Yeah. Sure. Where you at?
玻底加湾  乌巢旅馆
Bodega Bay. Crow's nest inn.
-你还在工作  -必须的
- You working? - Always.
你们离这近吗
You guys anywhere nearby?
-挺近的  -很好
- Near enough. - Cool.
在码头餐馆碰面怎样  一起吃午饭
Why don't we meet at the pier front restaurant -- lunch?
-一点见  -好  再见
- 1:00? - Yeah. Bye.
我们不该来这
We shouldn't be here.
是啊  我知道
Yeah. I know.
是警察吗
Cops?
你们不该来这
You shouldn't have come here.
[邪恶力量 第7季第19集]
看这个
Hey, get this.
迪克·罗曼又要资助一个考古挖掘项目
Dick Roman is funding another archaeological dig.
这货比狗仔队还能挖
Guy moves more dirt than "The drudge report."
有没有提到他要挖什么
Well, anything on what he's digging for?
我要看到了肯定会先说的
Don't you think I would have led with that?
安妮一般不迟到  对吗
Annie's not usually this late, is she?
从来不
No, never.
她有强迫症  我给她打个电话
She's totally compulsive. I'll try her cell.
她和鲍比有过一腿  你知道吗
You know, uh, you know she and Bobby had a thing, right?
是啊
Yeah.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I knew that.
真的吗
Really?
是啊
Yeah.
烽火战地情神马的  海明威格调的
Kind of a foxhole thing -- very Hemingway.
我和她也搞过一次"海明威"
She and I kind of went Hemingway this one time, too.
好吧
All right, well...
时有发生
That happens.
怎么  你也有过
What, you too?
是很久前的事了
Look, it was a while back.
我们正好在查同一个案子
We ended up on the same case.
她压力很大
She was stressed.
我
I-I-I...
我当时没有灵魂
I didn't...have a soul.
看来战地情略多啊
That's a lot of foxholes.
她不接
She's not answering.
敬阴魂已散的鬼魂们
Well, here's to ghosts that aren't there.
你听上去挺失望的
You sound kind of disappointed.
这样更好
Ah, it's better this way.
就算我很想再见他一面
I mean, even though I wish we could see him again
也不该如此
doesn't mean that we should.
我们是被放鸽子了吗
Are we being stood up?
是啊  希望只是如此
Yeah, let's hope that's all this is.
还是没通吗
Nothing?
直接进了语音信箱
Straight to voicemail.
有事不对劲
Something's not right.
她来玻底加湾干什么
What's she doing on Bodega Bay?
好像有活儿干  她没详说
She's working some kind of job. She didn't really say.
我得买酒了
I got to get a refill.
要我说
You know what, man?
也许你暂时把酒瓶收起来比较好
Why don't you just pack it away for a while?
这只会让你想起他  不是吗
All it does is remind us of him, you know?
是啊  我有想过  但是  时候未到
Yeah, I thought about that, but, uh...not yet.
我们去安妮的酒店房间看看
Let's go check out Annie's hotel room.
很久前这里发生过不少失踪悬案
These go back years -- disappearances never solved.
几十年前突然停止了
They stop a few decades back,
而最近又再次开始了
then pick up again just recently.
失踪的都是青少年
All teenagers.
安妮似乎发现一个他们失踪前
Looks like Annie found a spot a lot of them liked to poke around
常去的地方
just before they went missing.
是吗
Yeah?
是啊  凡·奈斯老宅
Yeah. Old Van Ness house.
各种好事
It's, uh, cheery.
警察去那儿搜查过  总是空手而归
Well, the police combed the place. They always come up dry.
是啊  警方的办事能力  我们都懂
Yeah, local law. Always on the ball.
伙计们
Guys...
是凡·奈斯家族在1862年修建的...
So, built in 1862 by the Van Ness family...
我刚才动了动窗帘
I just made that curtain shimmy.
你们就不能看看该看的地方吗
Could you look in the right place at the right time?
好几年前就挂出来卖  没人接手
Put up for sale a few years back. No takers.
可能是太毛骨悚然了吧
Probably 'cause it creeps their queso.
妈的  累死爹了
Balls, this is exhausting.
这么多年就一直在那儿  围着栅栏
It's just been sitting there, boarded up, for ages.
你看这个
Oh. Get this.
好像是几个月前
I guess a couple months back,
有人把它列入了
someone put it on one of those, uh,
"美国最恐怖鬼屋"的名单
"most haunted houses in america" lists.
我猜猜  正是开始有青少年失踪的时间
Let me guess -- that's when the teenagers started going missing.
-对  -很好
- Yep. - Okay.
咱们干活吧
Now let's get rolling.
我们干活吧
I say we get rolling.
蠢货
Idjits.
谢了
Thank you.
宝贝儿  我回来了
Honey, I'm home.
天啊
Geez.
我的同类啊
My people.
行了  我们走
All right, let's go.
我叫鲍比  我是鬼魂
I'm Bobby, and I'm a ghost.
能给咱稍微介绍一下这里吗
Hoping for a little ghost orientation here.
我叫鲍比
Je m'appelle Bobby.
真"热闹"
Chilly.
安妮
Annie?!
这里的反应很强烈
There's a whole lot of something going on.
我知道你昨晚做了什么
I know what you did last night,
你知道我对此是严令禁止
and you know it was forbidden!
我家里不允许发生这种事
I don't brook that sort of thing in my home.
下不为例  德克斯特  否则别怪我不客气
Don't do it again, Dexter, or there will be consequences.
最后一通电话就是打给我的
The call to me was the last one she made.
她到底去哪儿了
So where the hell is she?
鲍比
Bobby?
安妮
Annie!
我们到处找你呢
We've been looking for you.
你居然也来了
I can't believe you're here.
是啊  我死翘翘了
Yeah. I'm a doornail.
坏消息就是
Bad news here.
如果你看得见我  你也死翘翘了
If you can see me, you are, too.
死亡  鬼魂
Dead. Ghost.
我
Me.
谁都不希望这三个词出现在一起
Three words you never want to use in a sentence.
我感觉就像嗑了药
I feel like I was drugged.
我明白
I get it.
我大概一个月后才知道我还在人间
I figure it was a month before I even knew I was still here.
你算不错了
You're doing well.
-棒极了  -这么说
- Terrific. - So, uh...
你也把死神甩了吗
So, you duck your reaper, too?
什么  没有  压根没看见死神
What? No. I never even saw one.
你...
You --
鲍比
Bobby.
你从死神手里逃脱了
You ran away from your reaper?
故意的吗
On purpose?
所以你还在这儿
That's why you're still here?
-你这稀里糊涂的老疯子  -嘿
- You stupid, crazy old -- - Hey.
我记得你以前挺喜欢我这样的
I remember a time when you liked how crazy I was.
闭嘴吧
Oh, shut up!
真不敢相信
I can't believe you.
知道吗
You know what?
作为身不由己死掉的正常鬼魂
As a regular ghost with no choice in the matter,
我鄙视你
screw you.
我还有事情没做完  跟你一样
Hey. I got unfinished business here, Same as you.
这就是我没做完的事情
And there's my unfinished business right now.
孩子们
Kids!
听到没
Hello?
你们死了
You're dead.
算了  这俩人脑袋不太灵光
Well, they're not the brightest bulbs on the string.
我进来时  发现他们死了
I came in, they were roadkill.
然后有个大家伙朝我冲了过来
Then this big guy charges me.
于是我就...
And now I'm...
妈的
Crap.
难道就没点乐子吗
Is there a fun aspect to this?
没有吧
Not really.
而且到目前为止  我完全没搞懂规则
And so far, I can't crack the code on any of it.
我见过恶作剧鬼拿砸钢琴当热身运动
I mean, I've seen poltergeists bench a piano as a warm-up.
我就想帮帮俩孩子
I tried to help the boys out once
于是把桌上的书弄到了地上
by knocking a book off the table
结果足足晕厥了两个星期
and blacked out for two weeks.
这么说  萨姆和迪恩还不知道你在这儿
So, Sam and Dean don't even know you're here?
这真是够呛
Wow. That is messed up.
安妮  我把那些剪报发到你邮箱
Hey, annie, I'm e-mailing you those news clippings
这地方到处都是红的
We're redlining all over the place.
做最坏打算吗
Assume the worst?
是啊  总是这样
Yeah, always do.
好吧  怨魂
Okay. Vengeful spirit.
没准有一大堆呢  杀孩子
Maybe lots of them. Killing kids.
瞧瞧  没有血迹  什么都没有
Look around. No blood. No anything.
肯定没有尸体
Certainly no bodies.
如果魔鬼在这儿开联欢会
Well, if evil is partying here,
他的清洁队可真厉害
it's got a hell of a cleanup crew.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
怎么
What?
有情况
Here's something.
-是早几天打的电话  -听听
- From earlier this week. - Okay.
释放我
Free me.
是哪里打来的
Where'd that come from?
你见过这种手机号码吗
You ever seen a phone number look like that?
不错啊  酷毙了
All right, that's cool.
不好意思  嘿
Excuse me. Hey!
老大
Boss!
混蛋
Dick.
是啊  没办法
Yeah, well...
鬼魂可不是最喜欢跟人打交道的物种
Ghostsosin't the most sociable type to come down the pike.
不过既然他能做到...
But if he can do it...
妈的
Balls.
好优雅
Graceful.
新手
Novices.
你们都犯一样的错误
You all make the Same mistakes.
那么你一定很熟络了
Suppose you know all about it.
我都练了八十年了
Well, I've been at it 80 years.
我刚死不久
Yo, uh, fresh meat here.
还不知道发生什么事了呢
Not even sure what happened.
是吗
Really?
我头部中枪  什么都没感觉到
I got shot right in the melon, never felt a thing.
你呢
You?
1932年4月17日
I was stabbed brutally,
我就在这个吧台被人残忍地捅死
right here at this bar, April 17, 1932.
谁干的
Who done ya?
我真的很忙
I'm really very busy.
那这里怎么会有这么多死人的
How come there's so many dead folk in this place, anyway?
你知道吗
You know anything about that?
看来我们不应该谈论这事
I guess we're not supposed to talk about that.
抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我朋友很八卦  你叫
Uh, my friend is a little nosy, mister...?
克雷恩  哈斯克·克雷恩
Crane-- Haskel Crane.
哈斯克
Haskel...
你说的对
You're right.
我们俩是新手
We are novices,
拜托帮我个忙
so, could you do me a solid
教教我怎么搬动这张椅子
and show me how to move that chair?
就是张破椅子而已
It's one stupid chair.
一步一步慢慢来  美人
Baby steps, gorgeous.
先试试这个
Try this first.
你太焦虑了
You're angsting at it.
你知道沮丧会带给你什么吗
You know what getting frustrated will get you?
什么都没有
Nothing.
要移动东西有两个办法
You've got two ways to move things.
我用的方法  显然也是你必须做到的
What I did-- which you obviously must--
就是冷静下来
is calm yourself.
你是说  我们要用禅意来移动东西
You're saying we should move crap with the power of zen.
我的意思是  放松心情
I'm telling you to let go of all that.
冷静地告诉那东西要做什么
Calmly tell the thing what to do.
你紧张了
You're getting tense.
你在帮倒忙
You're not helpful.
选项二是什么  你说过有两种方法的
What's option 2? You said there were two ways.
你勃然大怒  火冒三丈的时候也行
Oh, you could use explosive anger and pure, red-hot rage,
但怒气是不能伪装的
but that's impossible to manufacture.
不好意思
Sorry.
有道理
Makes sense.
就像恶作剧鬼  心怀怨念之魂
Like poltergeists-- vengeful spirits.
我也怨念啊
I am vengeful.
你觉得我不会暴怒吗
You think I don't have red-hot rage?
我觉得你就是鬼魂中的败类
I think you're a sad excuse for one of us,
对于你的失败我一点都不惊讶
and I'm unsurprised that you're failing.
要不要我帮忙随便你
Take my help or don't,
不过如果你还想移动一个小跳蚤
But if you want to move a flea,
就乖乖听话
surrender.
先声明  我讨厌那个鬼片
For the record, I hated that swayze flick--
人鬼还言情啥的烂片
romantic bullcrap.
这到底是什么情况
What in cold hell was that?
你总有一日也会变成这样
That's you one day.
我们都会
That's all of us.
我们以不同的速度退化
We deteriorate at different rates--
有些早一点  有些晚一点
some sooner, some later.
但最终
And eventually all...
我们都会变成这样
like that.
灰飞烟灭
Nothing left at all.
鬼魂的老年痴呆症
Ghost Alzheimer's.
我真是越来越讨厌做鬼了
I'm liking this less.
我们找遍了这地方的每个角落
Well, that is every square inch of this place.
没有尸体  没有残肢  没有安妮
No bodies, no pieces of bodies-- no Annie.
雷声大雨点小啊
A whole lot of sizzle and no steak.
没消息也算是好消息吧
Well, maybe no news is good news.
什么意思
Meaning?
意思就是  也许她只是不在这里
Meaning maybe she's just not here.
也许她没事
Maybe she's still okay.
那你的直觉怎么说
Yeah, and what does your gut say?
我们还是去看看她的调查里还有些什么吧
Let's just see if there's anything else in her research.
萨姆  迪恩
Sam! Dean!
亲爱的  你以为我没试过吗
Honey, don't you think I've tried that?
我嗓子都吼哑了
I shouted myself hoarse.
但我就在这里
But I'm right here!
现在你知道那些想和我们
Well, now you know how all the ghosts
说话的鬼魂是什么感觉了
who have ever tried to talk to us feel.
你只能等着他们发现你
You just have to wait until they find you.
但我都不知道我在哪
But I don't even know where I'm at.
我把每间房都翻五遍了
And I've searched every room five times.
难怪他们就这样走了
No wonder they're walking away.
是我自我感觉良好  还是她真在打量我
Is it me, or am I being checked out?
不  汉子  她是在打量我
No, stud. I'm being checked out.
有事吗
Can I help you?
我叫维多利亚
I'm Victoria.
我是安妮
Annie.
我那天看到你了
I saw you here the other day.
我知道你是做什么的
I know the kind of work you do.
曾经是做什么的
Did.
我还在做着呢
Hey, I'm still doing it.
虽然在另一个次元里了
I mean, other-dimensionally speaking.
真棒
Attagirl.
等等  你的声音
Wait. Your voice.
你是给我打电话的那个人
You're the one on my phone.
你在这里的时候  我可以那样联络你
When you were here, I was able to call out to you that way.
鬼魂声音传递
Ah, spectral voice transference.
没错  鬼魂的小把戏
Right. Ghost juju.
对
Sure.
你说"释放我"是什么意思
So... W-what exactly did you mean when you said, "Free me"?
维多利亚  是什么束缚了你
Victoria, free you from what?
鲍比
Bobby!
安妮的情报是哪来的  我们知道吗
Where'd Annie get her intel? Do we know?
破酒瓶
Stupid flask.
玻底加湾遗产协会
Bodega Bay Heritage Society.
孩子们  拜托
Boys, come on.
该干的活儿在房子里呢
All the action's back in the pool.
走吧
Let's go!
可恶
Damn it.
这栋宅子的历史一直追溯到十九世纪中期
The house dates back to the mid-19th century.
迈尔斯·凡·奈斯淘金发了迹
Miles Van Ness made his fortune in the gold rush,
最后在玻底加湾安了家
eventually settling his family in Bodega Bay.
这宅子里发生过什么奇怪的事吗
Anything...unusual ever happen in the house?
一个世纪的时间长河中
Over the course of a century,
一栋宅子总会发生些事的
things are going to happen in a house.
"告诉它要做什么"
"Tell it what to do".
部分当地人发誓那里真的有鬼
Some locals swear it's haunted.
-动  -每个村里都有几个二逼
- Move. - Every village has its idiots.
我们只想听真正的猛料
We only want the real scoop, of course.
该死
Balls!
惠特曼·凡·奈斯
Whitman Van Ness.
家中的男孩也是继承人
Son and heir.
英俊  迷人
Handsome, charming,
一生却是个彻头彻尾的悲剧
dogged by tragedy all his life.
败光了家族财产  最后连宅子也没了
He lost the family fortune, then the house.
那里变成了妓院
It became a bordello.
直到四十岁死去  他一直都孤身一人
He lived in isolation till his death at age 40.
他还在那里呢
He's still there.
那个大块头是谁
Who's the, uh, the bruiser there?
德克斯特·欧康纳德是个囚犯
Dexter O'Connell. A convict.
一个极暴力的家伙
An extremely violent man.
他也在那儿
He's there, too.
凡·奈斯先生是个思想进步的人
Mr. Van Ness was socially progressive
对他心生怜悯
and took pity on him.
他是个看护员
He worked as grounds keeper.
德克斯特被判在惠特曼新婚前夕
Dexter was convicted for murdering Whitman's fiance
谋杀了他的未婚妻
on the eve of their wedding.
是这可怜人人生中的又一起悲剧
Another calamitous event in the poor man's life.
好  谢谢你
Well, thank you.
这宅子这周可真是火啊
The house is popular this week.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
前几天有个女士来问了许多问题
A lady came by the other day asking all sorts of questions.
-三十多岁  红发  很漂亮  -对
- Uh, 30's, red hair, good-looking? - Mmm.
我给你们的建议跟对她的一模一样
I gave her the same advice I'll give to you.
离那鬼地方远点
Stay away from the place.
那里非常的危险
It's extremely unsafe.
除了被判谋杀惠特曼的未婚妻
So, besides Whitman's fiance,
德克斯特·欧康纳德还被判
Dexter O'Connell was also convicted
谋杀了数个那家妓院的妓女
of killing a bunch of hookers who worked at the brothel.
他在被绞死前逃脱
He escaped before they could hang him.
但后来他又回到了那栋宅子
But then he returned to the house,
在那里被人用枪打死了
where he was found shot to death.
他为什么跑掉后
Why would he escape
又跑回去  被人抓住
and then go right back to the house where he got arrested?
我不知道
I don't know.
我还有好多事不知道呢
Add that to a list of things I don't know.
下一步打算怎么办
So what's the next move?
如果我可以的话
You know, if I could,
我愿意等到天荒地老  等你们俩搞清状况
I'd be getting old waiting on you two to figure this out.
好吧好吧
All right, now.
我杀得了狼人  修得好斑马车
I can kill werewolves, fix a Pinto,
烤得好玉米面包
and bake cornbread.
我要是做不到禅真见鬼了
I will be damned if I can't get zen.
我们把这段视频放上来是为了警告...
We're posting this video as a warning about...
也可能是纪念...
Or possibly a memorial to...
我们的朋友黛比·特伦和达利·斯考特
Our friends Debbie Tellen and Dudley Scott.
他们最后出现的地方是...
Last known whereabouts...
凡·奈斯大宅
The Van Ness house...
反正警察也不管这事儿...
Since the cops haven't done crap...
这或许是他们爱情故事终结的地方
In what may be the final moments of their love story.
他们俩差不多从八年级就在一起了
They've been together since like eighth grade.
没错  他俩进宅子后给我们发了短信
Yeah. They entered this house and texted us.
现在我们进去
We're going in.
萨姆
Sam?
怎么了
What?
告诉我这是你写的
Tell me you wrote that.
(安妮被困在大宅里)
不  不  不是我
No. No, I didn't.
他们走进了宅子
They came into the house...well...
好吧  那又会是谁
Then, who's there?
我说谁在这里
I said, who's there?!
(安妮被困在大宅里)
(鲍比)
鲍比
Bobby?
他们穿过了...
They walked through...
这些走廊
these halls...
寻找爱的小巢
Seeking a grotto of love.
你搞毛啊
Seriously?
鲍比
Bobby?!
是我
Yes.
我们一直都在说服自己他不存在
This whole time, we've been trying to talk ourselves out of it.
他就在...他怎么会在这儿
He's been-- What's he doing here?
-老兄  -咱们没时间扯这个
- Dude. - We don't have time for this!
赶紧滚回那栋宅子去
Get your asses back to that house!
我们得回那栋宅子去  赶紧的
We got to get back to that house, stat.
发生什么了
What happened?
是谁
Hello?
你们不该来这里
You shouldn't have come here!
德克斯特
Dexter.
我已经严令禁止了  够了
I expressly forbid you! Enough!
谢谢你
Thank you.
德克斯特  你想把他们吓跑
Dexter, you tried to warn them away.
这里的鬼已经够多了
You have enough of us.
他们还只是孩子  惠特曼
They're just children, Whitman.
我再也不能坐视不理了
I can't watch this happen all over again.
闭嘴
Shut up.
维多利亚  拿上摄像机
Ah, Victoria. Grab the camera.
我办不到
No. I can't.
我们不掺合惠特曼的事
We don't meddle in Whitman's affairs.
打住  真是的
Hold it. Let's get real.
是你向我发出了求救信号  现在我来了
You sent me the S.O.S., and now I'm here.
所以  还是搭把手
So, give me a hand.
但是现在他也能伤害你了
But now he can get you, too.
怎么伤害我  我已经死了
Get me how? I'm already dead.
好吧  你能告诉我
Okay, you want to help me understand
他到底把德克斯特怎么样了
exactly what did he do to Dexter?
惩罚了他
Punished him.
他想要警告这些人
He was trying to warn them.
他也曾试着警告你
He tried to warn you, too.
他把他吸干了
He drained him.
吸干  什么意思
Drained? What does that mean?
这就是他这么强大的原因
That's why he's so strong
所以你该躲着他
and why you should stay out of sight.
我们就是他的食物  再就是恶心的玩物
We're merely food to him -- food and perverse entertainment.
那之后发生了什么  就是烟消云散了
So, when he does that, what happens? Just...poof?
永远消失
Forever.
明白了  我还以为惠特曼是个可怜人
See, I thought that Whitman was some poor guy,
是德克斯特杀了他的未婚妻
and Dexter killed his fiance.
不是  惠特曼嫁祸给他
No. Whitman framed him.
是惠特曼杀了所有的人
Whitman killed all of us.
这里做妓院时  我在这儿做青楼女子
When this house was a brothel, I worked here as a fancy lady.
他割了我的喉咙
He slit my throat.
-"青楼女子"  你是个妓女  -积积口德
-"Fancy lady"? A hooker? -Please.
现在即使我们已经死了
And now, even in death,
每俘获一个灵魂  他的力量又强大一分
every soul he traps here makes him stronger.
既然这样  他把尸体藏在哪里
Okay, so, where does he keep the bodies?
我不知道
I don't know.
维多利亚  你可在这里呆了很久了
Victoria, you've been here forever.
我不会傻到跟踪他的
You don't follow him around.
听我说  我们会干掉这个人渣的
Listen, we are going to pull the plug on this bastard.
现在去把那该死的录像机捡起来
Now grab the damn camera.
天呐
Oh, dear.
他来了
It's him!
我们之前彻底搜过这里
We combed the crap out of this place.
如果安妮真的困在里面  我们却没找到她
If Annie's in there and we didn't find her...
那肯定是因为有东西不想让我们找到她
It's 'cause something didn't want us to.
好极了  明知宅有鬼  偏往里面闯吧
Awesome. Well, let's walk right into that.
-我来搜楼上  -好的
- All right, I'll check upstairs. - Yeah.
安妮
Annie?!
-对不起  臭小子  暂且别过  -安妮
- Sorry, boys. I'm leaving the pack. - Annie?!
-我是迪恩  萨姆也在  -安妮
- It's Dean! And Sam! - Annie?!
一点不奇怪
That's not odd.
萨姆  快下楼来
Sam, get back down here!
安妮
Annie?
有鬼在吗
Slimer?
-怎么了  -瞧瞧这个
- What? - Check it out.
他们爱情故事终结的地方
The final moments of their love story.
他们俩差不多从八年级就在一起了
They've been together since like eighth grade.
没错  他俩进宅子后给我们发了短信
Yeah. They entered this house and texted us.
我最讨厌这些独立电影  都是虚把式
Oh, I hate these indie films. Nothing ever happens.
他们走进了宅子
They came into the house.
他们穿过了...这些走廊
They walked through these halls.
等等  暂停一下
Wait, wait. Pause it.
向前倒一下
Frame back a little bit.
停
Stop.
她的确在这里  处境还不妙
She's here, and not in a good way.
给他们点时间反应一下
Give them a moment.
我死之后他俩迟钝多了
They've got a little slower since I left.
安妮
Annie?!
得想个法子让他们知道我就在这里
Got to let them know that I'm here.
你来做  我俩办不到
You have to do it. We can't.
-安妮  -这太危险了
- Annie?  - It's too dangerous.
这两人能帮助我们
These guys can help.
他们需要知道我们就在这里
They just need to know that we're here.
别害怕  我是维多利亚  维多利亚·陶德
Please. I'm Victoria -- Victoria Dodd.
你从哪里冒出来的
Where'd you come from?
就是这里
Here.
我曾是个青楼女子
I was a fancy lady.
妓女吗
A hooker?
安妮在这里吗
Uh, is Annie here?
是的
Yes.
你们看不到她
You can't see her.
不  你没踩在她身上
No, you're not standing on her.
-你就直说了吧  -我会的
- You want to just tell them? - I will.
我们那个时代  谈话的礼仪是很重要的
In my day, we believed in polite conversation.
安妮的处境非常危险
Annie's in terrible danger.
我们都很危险
We all are.
-谁在威胁你们  -惠特曼·凡·奈斯
- From? - Whitman van Ness.
但他已经死了
But he's dead.
你不是说他俩很有一手吗
I thought you said they were good.
我只是在消化这个消息  女士
Hey, I'm just processing, okay, lady?
他死了  你也已经死了
He's dead. You're dead.
什么叫"处境危险"
Define "terrible danger."
惠特曼控制着宅子里的所有人
Whitman has great power over all of us in the house.
是他杀了安妮
He killed Annie.
她说你们能释放我们
She says you can free us.
拜托了  你们必须
Please, you must --
维多利亚
Victoria?
我想她说的是真话
I'm gonna say she was telling the truth,
因为刚刚她的鬼魂都被灭了
considering that she just... got ghost-killed.
谁干的  惠特曼·凡·奈斯吗
So, what? Whitman van Ness?
至少我们知道要去谁的枯骨上撒盐  焚烧了
Now we know whose bones to salt and burn.
走吧
Let's go.
该死
Aw, hell no.
如果我没把酒瓶放在这儿
If I hadn't stashed that flask here,
我就能呆在萨姆和迪恩身边了
I'd still be glued to Sam and Dean.
聪明反被聪明误
Real clever.
-真有自知之明  -混蛋
- Actually was. - Son of a bitch.
我以为我们的唯一优势就是惠特曼那混蛋
I figured our one ace was that bastard Whitman
也无法离开这栋宅子
couldn't leave the house either.
很可能就像你和酒瓶的联系一样
Must have pulled a number like you and the flask.
说不定把什么东西放在小伙子们身上
Probably planted something on the boys.
-好极了  -听我说  亲爱的
- Terrific. - Hey, listen, sweetie --
你可以一整天都自怨自艾
You could beat yourself up all day about this,
但也可以利用惠特曼不在的良机
or we could take advantage of the fact that Whitman's gone,
干我们应该干的事情
do what we're supposed to do.
我们去一探究竟
Let's go figure this out.
你来吗  罗伯特
Coming, Robert?
我们把别的地方都搜过了
Well, we searched everywhere else.
我跟你说  惠特曼对这个房间严防死守
I'm telling you, Whitman guards his room like Fort Knox.
据我所知  鬼魂可不会怕冷
Last time I checked, ghosts didn't get cold.
没错  那是维多利亚
Yeah. That's Victoria.
这就是他杀死她的方法
That is how he took her out.
但他从哪里取出了她的尸体呢
But where did he get her corpse?
你说他把那两个男孩的尸体拖走了
Well, you said he dragged those two dead kids away.
运到哪里去了
Where'd he take them?
我不知道  我不敢冒险跟踪他
Yeah, I don't know. I couldn't risk following him.
你说过这栋宅子除了做过妓院外
What else did you say this place was,
还用来干过什么
other than a whorehouse?
干过好多事情呢
It was a lot of things.
做过公寓  寄宿学校
It was a boarding house, a school...
非法酒吧
A speakeasy.
说到非法酒吧
Yeah, well, thing about speakeasies --
肯定得藏很多东西
Hell of a lot to hide.
我还是很有一手的
Still got it.
这差不多就能说明问题了  是吧
Well, this pretty much tells the story, don't it?
你知道  我和你
You know, you and me --
我们烧过那么多尸骨
We burned our fair share of bones,
送一群鬼魂上路
sent a lot of ghosts packing.
当自己是被烧的那个  感觉有点不同
It's a little different when you're on the receiving end.
你说
So, uh...
他们都去哪了呢
what do you think happens to 'em --
进天堂  下地狱
Heaven, hell, or...
还是都不是
None of the above?
我不知道
I don't know.
很可能  就这样消失了
Just...gone, most likely.
我也是这么想的
Yeah, that's what I think, too.
这也是我想要的
That's what I want.
我想要一场猎人的葬礼
I want a hunter's funeral.
别惊讶了
Oh, come on.
那比现在可好多了
It's better than this --
困在这栋宅子里
Stuck to this house,
介乎于存在与不存在之间
somewhere between existing and not.
我想
No, I'm...
我已经准备好安息了
ready for some peace.
活着也没有太大意思
Wasn't much of a life.
我们这行很孤独
It was lonely, what we do.
但那是我自己选择的生活
Yeah, well, the life I had is the one I picked.
是啊  你还有那俩孩子
Yeah, but you had the boys.
而我就只有工作
All I had was work.
现在这也没有了
It's gone now.
但我的还没完
Yeah, well, I ain't done.
好吧  但我结束了
Okay, fine, but I am.
你现在比我强壮  鲍比
You're stronger than I am now, Bobby,
所以  你要帮我了却这个心愿
So, uh, you got to do this for me.
我们要去的是  镇边上的墓地
All right. Here we go -- cemetery, edge of town.
凡·奈斯家族在那儿有一个陵墓
The Van Ness family has its own mausoleum.
我们就放把火让那混蛋消失吧
All right, we light up the bastard and finish him off.
慢慢开  迟早能到的
Take it easy. We'll get there.
那不是我
Uh, that's not me.
怎么他会跟我们一起
Why's he with us?!
我不知道
I don't know.
肯定有什么东西在我们身上
There's got to be something on us!
萨姆
Sam!
成功了吗  甩掉他了吗
Did that do it? Did that get rid of him?
我不知道  我有不详的感觉
I don't know. I got a bad idea
我们刚刚把他送回老家了
we just snapped him back to his favorite house.
安妮还待在那儿
Where Annie's a sitting duck.
我们得马上找到骸骨  快
We got to find those bones. Come on.
我们开始点火吧
Let's build up the fire.
至少可以让一些可怜的灵魂得以安息
We can put some of these poor bastards to rest, at least.
开始火葬吧  时间不多了
Well, let's get to cremating. We ain't got all day.
喜欢我房间的风景吗
Enjoy the view from my room?
打算减少这里的人口吗
Planning to thin out the population?
你就这样回报我的招待吗
Is this how you repay my hospitality?!
不  我不愿走
No! I will not be taken!
我昏迷了多久
How long was I out?
一会了
A while.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
当然了
Sure.
我是说
I mean...
我死了
I'm dead,
是个鬼
I'm a ghost...
但还是蛮不错的
But, basically, swell.
你们好  孩子们
Hi, boys.
鲍比
Bobby?
等等
Wait.
你们看的到我吗
You can see me?
盯着人看不礼貌
You're staring, you know.
对了  安妮也在这儿
Annie's here, too, by the way.
你好  安妮
Hi, Annie. H-hi, Annie.
你们好
Hi, guys.
她说你俩长残了
She says you both look uglier than she remembered.
鲍比  你怎么会待在这儿
Bobby, h-how'd you stay here?
这个嘛
Yeah, well, uh...
去死吧  混蛋
Suck on that, swayze.
怪不得你老是不理我
That's why you never answered me.
我试着联系你
I tried calling you --
玩碟仙
The, uh, talking board,
做了那么多  但一直是我一个人
the works -- but I was always alone.
而迪恩总是把那东西放在他口袋里
Dean always had that thing in his pocket.
所以电磁波总是时有时无
That's why the EMF only went off half the time.
我们还以为是自己疯了
We thought we were going crazy.
那究竟发生了什么
S-so, what happened?
你是困住了  还是
Did you get stuck or -- or what?
我自己想留下
I wanted to stay.
-鲍比  -我要帮你们
- Bobby. - I need to help.
那也不能让你
Not if it means you have to...
变成这样
be this.
活着本就不易  死后不需安宁
Well, life wasn't comfy. Why should death be?
来吧
Now, come on.
安妮和我找到所有尸体了
Annie and I found all the bodies.
我们来让他们安息吧
Let's put 'em to rest.
别让酒瓶子掉火里面去了
And keep my damn flask away from the fire...
你懂的
Obviously.
你们来不来
Well, you coming?
我会想念她的
I'll miss her.
-我也是  -是啊
- Me too. - Yeah.
我跟她的交情可不一般
Well, you didn't know her like I did.
致安妮
Here's to Annie.
她得到了自己想要的猎人葬礼
She got the hunter's funeral she wanted.
跟当初我们为你办的一样
Kind of like the one we thought we gave you.
迪恩
Dean.
你是怎么想的  鲍比
What were you thinking, Bobby?
你现在本可在天堂里
You could be in heaven right now,
在乔和埃伦的酒馆喝啤酒  而不是困在
drinking beer at Harvelle's, not -- not stuck --
跟你们困在一起吗
Stuck here with you?
我们还要活儿要干
We still have work to do.
我只是觉得这很重要  迪恩
I just thought that was kind of important, Dean.
但这是不对的  你心里清楚
It's not right. You know that.
好吧  你都是对的
Sorry. You're right.
我怎么想的啊
What was I thinking?
你觉得我们该怎么办
So, what do you think we should do?
该做的我们都做了
We did what we should do.
现在我不知道了
Now I don't know.
你觉得我们还有可能
I mean, do you think it's possible we could --
或许跟他就这么好好相处吗
I don't know -- make it all work somehow?
我不知道  可能吧
I have no idea. Maybe.
闻所未闻
I've never heard of it.
但我知道的是
But you know what I do know?
事情不该是这样的
It ain't the natural order of things.
世间万物都该有终结
Everything is supposed to end.
他应该...
You know, he was supposed --
可现在
And now...
这样能有好结果吗
What are the odds this ends well?
能有吗
What are the odds?